## Caitlin Baker

E-mail: caitbaker@gmail.com Address: Dublin, Ireland Contact

Phone:  $+353\ 834777864$ Information

GitHub: github.com/caitbaker

LANGUAGE SKILLS Fluent in English, Portuguese and Spanish.

Professional Objectives

My main skillset lies within research, planning, marketing and customer service. I thrive to improve on these with each new career choice.

I am a fast problem solver and have an ability to learn new skills in a short period of time as proven by having successfully moved to multiple countries to live, work and study. I am relentlessly resourceful and I am currently learning how to code, as I see technology been at the centre of interesting new developments within my chosen areas of interest.

I am a very communicative person and like teamwork but also work well alone, as you can see in my experience below.

EDUCATION

Dalarna University, Borlange, Sweden

Master of Arts (MA), Tourism Destination Development

Ongoing

Escola Superior de Tecnologia e Gestao, IPVC, Viana do Castelo, Portugal

BA in Tourism 2004 - 2008

Professional EXPERIENCE

Nexeo Solutions Central Office Europe, Barcelona, Spain

Customer Service Representative

June 2012 - June 2013

Back office management and support for Portuguese sales team.

Inputting orders into SAP.

Management of customers' e-mails, faxes and phone calls.

Hotusa Hotels S.A., Barcelona, Spain

Hotel Reservations Agent

December 2011 – February 2012

Reserving accommodation for clients and agencies via telephone and e-mail.

Answering inquiries pertaining to hotel services, C2B and C2C.

Luxottica Iberica S.A., Barcelona, Spain

July 2011 – November 2011 Call Centre Agent

Customer service B2B through phone, e-mail and fax.

Inputting orders and resolving problems.

Groundforce, Barcelona, Spain

Check-in Agent January 2011 - May 2011

Passenger and baggage check-in.

Passenger boarding.

Customer service.

## Ryanair Ldt., Stansted Airport, United Kingdom

 $Cabin\ Crew$ 

September 2009 - March 2010

Passenger service.

Operational and security processes.

Problem solving.

On board sales.

Computer

Microsoft Office, Latex, SAP and SFDC.

SKILLS

Hobbies Reading, travelling, hiking, spending time with friends, listening to music and dancing.

Referees Available on request.